Edward C. Blomeyer photographic collection, Inclusive: 1906-1923, Bulk: 1912-1920
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Texas., 1906-1920; 2
  - Waco, 1912-1920; 1
    - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges, 1912-1920; 1
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges 507-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-507.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:16)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-Wooded Scene, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:17)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:18)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Indian Spring Park 816-9; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-816.9.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:19)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-View of River from Cliffs, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:20)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-Trails, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:21)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges. Cameron Park-View from east side of river 882-2; tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-882.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:22)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-View from east side of river 882-3; tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-882.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:23)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Indian Spring Park 062-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-062.1.tif, 1918 May 5 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:24)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park (road through), 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:25)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Waco Suspension Bridge (Flood) 953-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-953.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:26)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Waco Suspension Bridge (Flood) 953-2; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-953.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:27)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Waco Suspension Bridge (Flood) 953-3; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-953.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:28)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Waco Suspension Bridge 812-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-812.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:29)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Waco Suspension Bridge 813-2; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-813.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:30)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Waco Suspension Bridge 810-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-810.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:31)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Interurban Bridge 703-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-703.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:32)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Interurban Bridge (Flood) 500-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-500.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:33)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Washington Avenue Bridge (Flood) 694-2; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-694.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:34)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Washington Avenue Bridge (Low Water) 705-2; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-705.2.tif, 1917 February 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:35)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Railroad Bridges and Brazos River 766-3; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-766.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:36)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Railroad Bridges, Brazos River, low water 813-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-813.1.tif, 1917 December 23 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:37)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River-high water, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:38)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River trail entrance-Cameron Park 890-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-890.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:39)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River Jetty?, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:40)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River Jetty 909-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-909.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:41)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River Jetty, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:42)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River-high water 814-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-814.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:43)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River-high water and flooded structure 758-3; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-758.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:44)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River-low water 815-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-815.1.tif, 1917 February 10 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:45)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River? from trail 765-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-765.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:46)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Brazos River Dam? 764-2; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-764.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:47)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Bosque River and Bridge, 1917 June 7 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:48)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Bosque River and Bridge 803-3; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-803.3.tif, 1917 August 26 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:49)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Bosque River and Bridge, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:50)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Rivers, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Bridges, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train, 1918; 2
      On June 18, 1918, troop train number 264, carrying soldiers from the 80th Field Artillery, which was posted at Camp MacArthur, left Waco, Texas, traveling eastward on the Cotton Belt rail line, derailed in the nearby town of Selby. The Waco News-Tribune, June 19-20, 1918, states that the accident caused the deaths of 2 troops: Corporals Laurn Harrell and August Handschumacher, Jr. Additionally, about 30 military personnel and 4 employees of the railroad were injured. The wreckage of the derailment is documented by E.C. Blomeyer in this series of photographs.
      The derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train no. 264, near Waco, Texas, is shown. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-433.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, June 1918.
      The derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train no. 264, near Waco, Texas, is shown. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-439.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, June 1918.
      The derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train no. 264, near Waco, Texas, is shown. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-435.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, June 1918.
      The derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train no. 264, near Waco, Texas, is shown. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-439.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, June 1918.
      The derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train no. 264, near Waco, Texas. The wreckage of the St. Louis Southwestern Railway of Texas, #510, Baldwin steam locomotive is shown. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-435.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, June 1918.
      The derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train no. 264, near Waco, Texas. The wreckage of the St. Louis Southwestern Railway of Texas, #510, Baldwin steam locomotive is shown. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-438.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, June 1918.
      The derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train no. 264, near Waco, Texas. The wreckage of the St. Louis Southwestern Railway of Texas, #510, Baldwin stefam locomotive is shown. The digital image isrom a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-434.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, June 1918.
      The derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train no. 264, near Waco, Texas, is shown. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-437.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, June 1918.
      The derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train no. 264, near Waco, Texas, is shown. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-440.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, June 1918.
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 434-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-434.2.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 54)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 434-1 Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-434.1.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 55)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 435-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-435.1.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 56)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 435-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-435.2.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 57)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 433-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-433.1.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 58)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 437-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-437.2.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 59)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 438-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-438.2.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 60)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 439-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-439.1.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 61)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 439-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-439.2.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 62)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train 440-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-440.1.tif, 1918 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 63)
      - Waco: Derailment of Camp MacArthur Troop Train, 1918 June 18 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry, 1912-1920; 3
      The photographs in this group demonstrate the importance of the cotton industry in Waco and McLennan County. The cotton yard that was once located in downtown Waco in the area of Second and Jackson through Clay streets is shown stocked with many bales of cotton ready for market.
      Waco was home to the Texas Cotton Palace, an annual event that drew tens of thousands of people annually for several years; an image of the main building is shown. Additionally, this series contains images of the annual Cotton Palace Parade making its way on Austin Avenue. Texas Governor Jim Ferguson is photographed participating in this event.
      These vehicles are uniquely decorated for the Texas Cotton Palace Parade. The middle vehicle is advertising Independent Telephone Companies in South and North Texas and the other two the Brazos Valley Telegraph and Telephone Company. This digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-706.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915, in Waco, Texas.
      This image was taken in the vicinity of the cotton yard that was located at South Second and Clay Streets, Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-722.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915.
      This vehicle is uniquely decorated for the Texas Cotton Palace Parade. It is advertising Independent Telephone Companies in South and North Texas. This digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-708.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915, in Waco, Texas.
      The Texas Cotton Palace Parade makes its way westward on Austin Avenue, the Amicable (Alico) Building can be seen in the distance. This digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-502.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915.
      The Texas Cotton Palace Parade makes its way west on Austin Avenue, Waco, Texas. This digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-501.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915.
      This image is of the main building of the Texas Cotton Palace located in Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-689.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915.
      Texas Governor Jim Ferguson is seen here riding in the Texas Cotton Palace parade as his wagon makes its way on Austin Avenue, Waco, Texas. This digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-505.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915.
      This image shows a cotton yard that was located in the area of South Second and Jackson Streets, Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-505.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915.
      This image was taken in the vicinity of the cotton yard that was located near South Second and Clay Streets, Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-504.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915.
      This image was taken in the vicinity of the cotton yard that was located near South Second and Clay Streets, Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-720.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915.
      Texas Governor Jim Ferguson is seen here riding in the Texas Cotton Palace parade as his wagon makes its way on Austin Avenue, Waco, Texas. This digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-504.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915.
      The Texas Cotton Palace Parade is shown with what is believed to be troops from the Texas National Guard walking westward on Austin Avenue, Waco, Texas. This digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-692.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1915, in Waco, Texas.
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Austin Avenue Cotton Palace Parade 2:64, 1915 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:64)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Austin Avenue Cotton Palace Parade 2:65, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:65)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Austin Avenue Cotton Palace Parade, Gov. Ferguson 505-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-505.2.tif, 1915 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:66)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Austin Avenue Cotton Palace Parade, Gov. Ferguson 504-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-504.1.tif, 1915 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:67)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton in storage 504-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-504.2.tif, 1916 September 30 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:68)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade, soldiers marching down Austin Avenue 760-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-760.2.tif, 1915 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:69)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade, soldiers marching down Austin Avenue: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-503.1.tif, 1915 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:70)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-Up Austin and Alico in background 502-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-502.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:71)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-View of soldiers and Interurban on Austin Avenue 692-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-692.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:72)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-Soldiers with flags 760-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-760.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:73)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-Up Austin Avenue 501-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-501.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:74)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-Tel. Co. float 706-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-706.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:75)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-Tel. Co. float 706-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-706.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:76)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-Tel. Co. float 753-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-753.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:77)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-Tel. Co. float 708-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-708.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:78)
      - Waco: Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-Tel. Co. float 689-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-689.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:79)
      - Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade-Butterfly Float 793-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-793.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:80)
      - Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:81)
      - Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Cotton Palace Parade, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:82)
      - Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Waco Cotton Yard 505-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-505.1.tif, 1916 September 30 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:83)
      - Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Waco Cotton Yard 720-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-720.2.tif, 1916 July 3 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:84)
      - Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry: Waco Cotton Yard and horse 722-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-722.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:85)
      - Texas Cotton Palace and Parade, Cotton Industry, 1912-1920 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - General, 1912-1920; 4
      This group of pictures includes scenes of Waco's military bases such as Camp MacArthur and Rich Field. Other images show auto races, street scenes, the Shakespeare monument, and bird's eye views of downtown. Additionally, the remains of the Huaco Clubhouse after a fire destroyed it are included.
      The Shakespeare monument on Riverside Drive (University-Parks) is shown soon after construction. Its plaque reads: "'Immortal Be His Name-Waco Shaksepere [SIC] Club, 1899-1916." Digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-705.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      Telephone Building bird's eye view: on the left is St. Mary's Catholic Church and to the right is Sacred Heart Academy on Washington Avenue; Waco High School is seen in the distance. The Texas Telephone Company building's rooftop which gave this vantage point is located at 119 North 9th Street. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-803.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
      Auto Race: In Waco's Gurley Park, a fifty-mile auto race used to be held. These photographs taken at Gurley are believed to be competing in this particular event. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-725.2.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      Camp MacArthur: Pictured are U.S. Army field artillery soldiers at Camp MacArthur training on the range. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-760.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
      Street Scene: E.C. and Amma Blomeyer go for a drive in their Ford Model-T. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ½ by 3 ½ -inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-695.2.tif, circa 1912.
      Street Scene: E.C. Blomeyer hand cranks his Ford Model-T while wife, Amma, looks on. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ½ by 3 ½ -inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-695.3.tif. Date is circa 1912.
      Auto Race: In Waco's Gurley Park, a fifty-mile auto race used to be held. These photographs taken at Gurley are believed to be competing in this particular event. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-724.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      Rich Field: This photo shows a crashed Army Air Corp bi-plane from Rich Field. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-720.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917
      Rich Field: This photo shows an Army Air Corp bi-plane from Rich Field. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-909.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
      Telephone Building bird's eye view: downtown Waco looking towards the Amicable Building from the Texas Telephone Company's rooftop, the building is located at 119 North 9th Street. Digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-496.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
      Auto Race: In Waco's Gurley Park, a fifty-mile auto race used to be held. These photographs taken at Gurley are believed to be competing in this particular event. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-725.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      - Waco: General: Auto Race 726-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-726.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:86)
      - Waco: General: Auto Race 699-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-699-2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:87)
      - Waco: General: Auto Race 696-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-696.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:88)
      - Waco: General: Auto Race, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:89)
      - Waco: General: Auto Race 725-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-725.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:90)
      - Waco: General: Auto Race 725-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-725.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:91)